翻译校对       Mam
日  听      HARERE
日听校对       Syura
翻译        小袖
时间轴       卡卡
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
"Newspaper Club"
President,
部長 ついに購読者が一桁となりました
our circulation has finally
dropped to single digits.
"Alien city discovered
at Ouran Elementary!!"
Report the exact numbers to me.
正確な数を報告なさい
How many newspapers
did we sell this week?
今週の新聞はどれくらい売れたのですか
Two copies.
２部です
That's all?
たったの？
Two copies.
２部です
Ukyo- kun, did you buy one?
右京君 君は買いましたか
買いました
Yes, I did.
Sakyo- kun, did you buy one?
左京君 君は買いましたか
Yes, I did.
買いました
では 部員以外は誰も買ってないということですね
Then, you're saying that
no one outside the club bought one?
To report it precisely,
that is what it means.
正確に報告すれば そういうことになります
This is a problem.
困りましたね
来週号が一学期最後の新聞になります
Next week's edition will be
the last one of the first term.
If we don't come up with slightly
better results before summer vacation,
夏休み前にもう少しいい結果を出さないと
the club will shut down
before the end of the term.
今学期限りが廃部となってしまいます
By the way, how are they doing?
ところで あれはどうなんです
ちなみにホスト部の写真集
"I Love Love Love Tamaki Special!"
I might mention that
the Host Club's photo collection,
『スキスキ環くんスペシャル』は
sold out all 1000 copies
as soon as it went on sale.
発売と同時に一千部が完売しています
"Moe- Moe Ouran Diaries:
Glasses Special Feature!"
宝積寺蓮華が個人的に出している同人誌
The dojinshi that Hoshakuji
Renge put out on her own,
『萌え萌え桜蘭日記』第八号も
also sold out as soon
as it went on sale yesterday,
昨日 発売と同時に完売し
and is already into its second printing.
すでに増刷がかかっています
Is that so?
そうですか
They are the ones who have
the influence, are they?
やはり勢いは彼らにありますか
- Welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
"The Host Club is now open for business"
We mustn't, Tamaki-sama.
行けませんわ環様
the many other girls that long for you
これ以上近づけば
あなたをお慕いする数多の女性に恨まれてしまいます
will resent us.
姫
My princess, these hydrangeas
今ならば このあじさいが我々の姿を隠してくれるでしょう
will keep us hidden for the time being.
For this moment, at least,
I am yours alone.
この一時だけは君だけの僕
Yes, for this moment, as the spirits
そう あじさいの精霊が見方するこの時だけは
of the hydrangeas stand by us.
Tamaki-sama, I yearn to be with you!
"Forbidden Rendezvous Play"
環様 お慕い申しております
My princess!
姫
Oh, my!
"Shell matching"
Sorry about that!
ごめんあそばせ
I lose again?
また僕の負け
Princesses, go easy on him, okay?
姫たち お手柔らかにね
Kaoru is quite the crybaby.
馨のやつ 泣き虫だから
Hikaru! You liar!
光 嘘つけ 誰が泣くって
Who are you calling a crier!?
So you say, but when
it's just the two of us,
とか何とか言って
僕と二人っきりで罰ゲームしたら
playing punishment games,
then what happens, Kaoru?
どうなっちゃうんだっけな 馨は
B-but Hikaru, that's because you...
だ だって あれは光が
What!? What!?
なになに なにがあったの
What happened!?
My, since when did the inner garden
have this fantastic little stream?
中庭にこんな素敵な小川が いつの間に
It's called a yarimizu channel.
遣り水というのですよ
It's said that during the Heian era,
曾て平安人は
people would get a sense of the four
seasons from the flower petals
この水面に漂う花びらや紅葉に四季を感じ取ったと言います
and autumn leaves that
drifted along these waters.
I had this made, out of my desire
to spend the four seasons
姫たちと四季を共にしたいという願いを込めて作らせて頂きました
together with you, my princesses.
"Reservation book"
つきましてはいかがでしょう
On that subject, what do you say?
In the fall,
秋にまた限定少人数で紅葉のお茶会でも
we're having an autumn leaves tea party
for a limited number of people.
"Sign me up!"
"Reservation book"
We'll make reservations!
予約します
The two of us under this coat
will now eat soba noodles!
二人織でお蕎麦を食べます
Uh-oh!
How cute!
かわいい
It's so peaceful. I guess that's
what acclimation will do for you.
のどかだなあ
さすがに慣れってやつかな
It's been like this ever since
I got into this school, after all.
入学以来ずうとこの調子だからな
ハルヒ 伏せろ
Haruhi! Duck!
Hikaru! You came this close to snuffing
out the light of Haruhi's life!
光 危うくハルヒの命の灯火が消えかけたぞ
I thought this was supposed
to be peaceful...
のどかじゃなかったのか
Huh? Sir, it's your own fault
for not catching it, isn't it?
殿がちゃんと受け止めないのが悪いんじゃん
If you can't even play kemari very well,
手鞠も満足にできないなんて
then I weep for your reputation
as Ouran's resident "Hikaru Genji."
桜蘭の光源氏の名がなくね
何
What!?
It appears that if the Newspaper
Club is to continue,
新聞部の存続のため
we will have to make our request of them.
ここは彼らに頭を下げるしかないようですね
Please wait, President!
待ってください部長
It's too dangerous
to get involved with that club!
あの部にかかるのは危険すぎます
Never mind the club being closed,
場合によっては 廃部どころか退学の恐れも
you could be expelled!
What!? Then, try catching this!
何だと ならばこれを受け止めてみよ
Starlight Kick!!
スターライトキック
何
What!?
速い
That's fast!
Take care!
達者でなあ～
"But no control..."
There is nothing to worry about.
心配することはありません
彼らといかに関わっても
I'm not about to let myself come to harm
by getting involved with-
それで損害を被るような私…
President!
部長
I'm terribly sorry about that.
誠に申し訳ありませんでした
No, not at all.
いえいえ そんな
It was just a mari ball
breaking through the window,
たかが窓ガラスが割れて 鞠が頭に直撃しただけですから
and hitting me right on the head.
S-sorry!
す すみません
"Ouran Academy Newspaper Club President
Akira Komatsuzawa, High School 3rd-Year"
However, this works out perfectly.
しかしちょうどよかった
In fact, I was just thinking
about asking the Host Club
実はホスト部にぜひ
"Newspaper Club Member
Chikage Ukyo, High School 2nd-Year"
取材協力をお願いできないかと思っていたところでしてね
High School 2nd-Year"
"Newspaper Club Member
Tomochika Sakyo, High School 2nd-Year"
to let us do a story on you.
You mean there's a Newspaper Club here?
新聞部なんてあったんだ
"Teacher is growing hair!"
Well, there's this, anyhow.
つってもこれだけどね
"Discord in the football club!?"
"Teacher is growing hair!"
We call it the "Ou-spo."
通称桜スポ
"Toupee!?"
It covers the school's love affairs,
校内恋愛事情だとか
class divisions caused by family
power struggles, and so on.
"Love across social classes!!"
家同士の権力抗争によるクラス内分裂とか
It's a gossip paper, specializing
in excessively stirring up scandals.
過剰に煽りまくったスキャンダル専門のゴシップ誌だよ
"Discord in the football club!?"
It's all made up,
so no one reads it anymore.
捏造ばっかで もう誰も読んでないけどね
It's true, we've lost sight of the truth
確かに我々は注目を集めたいばかりに真実を見失っていました
as we've focused on getting attention.
しかしこうして廃部寸前に追い込まれて
However, with us being this
close to getting shut down,
our eyes have finally been opened.
ようやく目が覚めたのです
We have realized what it is that
我々が取材し報道すべきものが何であるかに気づいたのです
we should be covering, and reporting on.
We beg you,
お願いします
for the last paper of 1st term,
一学期最後の新聞はぜひ
we would like you to let us reveal
the truth behind your charm,
ホスト部密着取材特集号で
皆様の魅力の真実に迫りたいと思っています
in an up-close, special edition
covering the Host Club.
Please, offer us your help.
どうか我々に力をお貸しください
Just leave it to me.
お任せ下さい
I would be happy to accept-
その話 お引き受けします
We must decline.
お断りします
Kyoya! He got hurt because of me!
鏡夜 俺のせいで彼は怪我を
Unfortunately, we limit any information
生憎ですが
うちの情報公開はお客様限定とさせていただいております
about us to our guests.
その怪我の治療費などは またご相談ということで
We will gladly agree to pay any costs
related to treating your injury.
Yeah. I don't think there is any benefit
だよな いままでさんざんでたらめ書いてたとこに協力して
in helping you out,
after so much of the
nonsense you have written.
僕らのメリットがあるとも思えないし
Not only that,
つうか 僕ら他人に迷惑をかけるやつって
we're just not much for people
who make trouble for others.
だめなんだよね
It's frightening how some
people don't look inward.
自分を省みないって恐ろしいな
Is that so?
そうですか
I guess you really can't erase
the sins of the past, huh?
やはり過去の罪は消せないのですね
You can't get people to offer you
それを償う機会を与えてもらうことはできないんですね
a chance to redeem yourself, huh?
Aah!! The pain in my head!
頭の痛みが
President!
部長
Thank you, Ukyo- kun, Sakyo- kun.
ありがとう 右京君 左京君
Aah!! No, I'm still lightheaded!
やっぱりめまいが
President!
部長
I'll be fine... aah!!
大丈夫ですよ
President!
部長
Unfortunately, all we can do now
is disband with grace...
残念ですが もう潔く廃部にするしか
That is not so!
そんなことはない
People can always make a fresh start.
人は必ずやり直せる
Very well.
良かろう ホスト部の総力を結集し
We will rally the strength
of the Host Club,
and work all-out to re-establish
the Newspaper Club!
新聞部の立て直しに全面協力すると
Not us.
僕らやんないよ
We'll never be able to go along
そんなに毎回殿のお人好しに付き合ってたらきりがないの
with how trusting you always are, sir.
Besides, it's too much trouble.
つうか面倒じゃん
We're leaving, Tamaki.
帰るぞ 環
We're holding an evaluation
meeting in the club room,
部室で今日の反省会をやる
mostly about you.
主にお前の
Hold it!
待ってぇ
お前らには血も涙もないのか
Have none of you any humanity?
Can you look on them,
廃部に追い込まれる彼らを見て
being forced to close down their club,
and not take any pity on them?
かわいそうとも思わんのか
Their house is breaking up!
一家離散なんだぞ
"Unclear what that means"
This is an order from the club president!
これは部長命令だ
I will not allow you to refuse.
断ることは許さん
We refuse!
"Flatly!!"
お断りします
"Music Room #3"
あからさまに怒ってるよ
He's clearly upset at us.
He hasn't even changed his clothes.
着替えもしないで
He's acting like a child,
being right near us,
すごく近くにいるがあえて目を合わせないという
yet not looking us in the eye.
子供の喧嘩だな
Tama-chan gets lonely easily, after all.
環ちゃんは寂しがり屋さんだからね
Club activities are like a family...
部活とは家族なのに
So a club shutting down
is like a house breaking up...
だから廃部は一家離散なのに
かわいそうなのに
Those poor guys...
新聞部に協力してあげるのってそんなにダメなんですか
Would it really be so bad
to help out the Newspaper Club?
Oh?
How uncommon, you taking
his highness's side.
珍しく殿サイドじゃん
That's not what I'm doing.
そういう訳じゃないけどさ
I'm just unusually confident
that before long,
そのうちチラチラこちらを小犬のような目で見始めて
he's going to start glancing over
this way with his puppy-dog eyes,
結局こっちが折れざるを得なくなるという妙な確信が
and we won't be able to help
ourselves but cave in to him.
You've certainly gained
some experience points, huh?
お前 確実に経験値積んでるなあ
Besides, Hikaru, isn't this the sort
of thing you guys typically go in for?
それに 光たちだって普段なら乗りそうな話じゃない
Not especially. This time,
it'll be nothing but trouble.
別に 今回は面倒なだけ
ハニー先輩たちは
Honey- senpai, what about you guys?
Well you see,
あのね 僕ケーキ食べなきゃならないからね
I have all this cake that
I need to eat, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Those are the eyes.
あの目だ
Puppy-dog eyes.
小犬の目だ
There will be some conditions.
条件をつけるぞ
Woof!
The outline for the special feature
articles will be submitted by us.
特集記事の企画はこちらで提示したものにすること
Interviews will be
cardinally prohibited.
基本的にインタビューは禁止
接客風景もお客様にご迷惑だからアウトだ
Views of us entertaining the customers
will be intrusive to them,
so they are out.
Woof woof!
Is that okay with everyone?
皆もいいな
Well, if you say so, Kyoya- senpai...
まあ 鏡夜先輩が言うなら
...then fine.
いいけど
If Kyo-chan says so, then I'm okay.
鏡ちゃんが言うならいいよ
Mm-hmm.
That's the shadow- king for you.
さすが影のキング
Why, of course. If you will
allow us to cover you,
もちろんです
取材をさせていだだけるなら条件は守ります
we will observe your conditions.
Well then, you may start tomorrow.
では 取材は明日からということで
How is that bump on your forehead doing?
額の傷の具合はどうですか
Oh, this little thing is no big deal.
なあに こんなのどうってことないですよ
On the contrary,
it's because of this bump
むしろこの怪我のおかげで ご縁ができて感謝したいくらいです
that we have come together,
so I am grateful for it.
We really are sorry about it.
本当に申し訳ありませんでした
"First-aid kit"
Please at least use this medication,
by way of apology from me.
せめてものお詫びに この薬をお使いください
This is a first-aid treatment set,
made by my family's company.
うちの会社で作っている救急医療セットです
Thank you so much.
どうもすみません
Well, if you'll excuse me...
では 失礼します
Oh, Otori- kun...
鳳君
You come from the family
of the Otori Group,
君はあの医療機器メーカー 鳳グループのご子息でしたね
the ones who make
medical equipment, right?
Our main occupation
is in hospital administration.
本業は療院経営ですが
I am so glad that we
have come together.
お近づきになれて嬉しいですよ
My father is the president
of Komatsuzawa Publishing.
うちの父親はあの小松沢出版の社長です
Yes, I am aware of that.
ええ 存じております
Are you serving as
Newspaper Club president
新聞部部長をなさっているのは 将来跡を継ぐ時の準備ですか
to prepare you for when you
take over for him in the future?
Yes, well, I have this
younger brother, you see.
ですが私には弟がおりましてね
He is quite a bright lad, too.
これがなかなかできのいいやつでして
父は将来出版社の経営をすべてその弟に任せるつもりなんです
Father plans to turn all management
of the publishing firm over to my brother.
Passing over me, the older brother...
兄であるこの私を差し置いてですよ
However, if I am able to serve
out my third year at Ouran Academy
ですがもし私がこの桜蘭学院で三年間新聞部の部長を務めあげれば
as the president of the Newspaper Club,
he may reconsider,
将来の後継者候補を考えなおしてくれるかもしれない
and make me a candidate
to succeed him in the future.
Do you understand?
わかりますか
I cannot allow this club
to disband, no matter what.
絶対にこの部を廃部にはできないんです
Excuse me.
失礼します
部長は鳳鏡夜に取り入ろうとなさったんですか
President, were you trying
to curry favor with Otori Kyoya?
そう 私の敵は須王環だけですよ
Yes. My only foe is Suou Tamaki.
I was going to use the power
of the school newspaper
本来なら 校内新聞の力で
to become a popular figure
on campus, but then...
私がこの学院の人気物になるはずだったのに
Suou Tamaki butted in
with his Host Club,
あの須王環が突如立ち上げたホスト部が瞬く間に人気を集めてしまった
and garnered all that popularity
in the blink of an eye.
Even before Suou enrolled at this school...
須王が入学する前から
...we had heard that the President's
newspaper was unpopular.
部長の作る新聞は人気がなかったと聞いていますが
Be quiet!
お黙りなさい
If I ask Mama, I can have all dealings
私がママに頼めば
うちの出版社と君たちの家との取引をすべてなしにできるんですよ
between our publishing firm
and your houses cut off.
I swear, I will expose
their special standing,
必ず尻尾を掴んでやります
not being affiliated with either
the sports clubs or the cultural clubs,
運動部にも文化部にも属さず 顧問すらいないその特殊態勢
and not even having
an advisor over them!
Club activities where false
affections are peddled?
恋愛詐欺まがいの部活動
The extent of their audacity
could only be attributed
あそこまでの傍若無人ぶりは 須王の権力誇示にほかなりません
to Suou flaunting his power.
I'm sure he uses his parents' authority
to make his companions follow him,
奴はきっと親の権威で仲間を従わせて
and do whatever he likes with the girls.
女子をすき放題にしているんです
Starting with Otori Kyoya,
あの鳳鏡夜を始め
ホスト部員たちは本来なら私の部下になるべき連中です
the Host Club members should have
been club members under me!
I'm afraid that Suou Tamaki
is quite shrewd.
須王環
恐らくは相当の切れ者ですよ
Ordinarily, he acts like
such an affable character,
普段はお人好しキャラを演じていますが
but he most definitely has a dark side.
奴には絶対裏がある
I'm going to make sure
I come up with some scandal,
必ずスキャンダルをモノにし
思い知らせてやります
and teach him a lesson!
だるまさんがころんだ
The Daruma doll fell over!
- Hikaru! Kaoru! I saw you move!
- President, what on earth
光 馨 今ちょっと動いただろう
部長 これは一体何の光景でしょうか
へーん 動いてません
are we watching here?
Could it be some new religion?
新手の宗教でしょうか
There's no reason
I should know, is there?
私にわかるわけがないでしょう
I can't blame you for being surprised.
驚かれるのも無理はない
This game has been passed down
through antiquity by commoners.
これは古くから庶民に伝わる遊びでしてね
他にも庶民の遊びには
There are many other games
that commoners play
where you can have fun all by yourself,
お金を使わず身一つで楽しめるものがたくさんあるのですよ
without spending any money.
And what does this have
to do with any of our coverage?
それがうちの取材とどういう関係が
親しみやすさ
Accessibility!
In order to wipe out the negative
image that the Newspaper Club has,
新聞部のマイナスイメージを払拭し
and claim your readership once again,
再び読者をつかむためには
accessibility is indispensable!
親しみやすさが不可欠
This is indeed according to my plan.
これぞまさに計算どおり
"The handsome boys of the Host Club
enjoy commoners' games"
Showing the handsome boys of the Host Club
enjoying commoners' games,
庶民の遊びに興じるホスト部美男子たち
coupled with the fresh
outdoors of early summer,
屋外で初夏の爽やかな背景も相まって
一面を飾るにぴったりな麗しさ
will be the perfect thing
to give your front page a facelift.
Plus, this dream-like plan also
lets you show some of the commoners,
おまけに一部の庶民も久々に童心に帰れて大喜び
who are thrilled to return
to their childhood!
という夢のような企画なのだ
Wow, he's looking at me.
なんか見てる
I wonder if I should be thrilled now?
大喜びしなきゃいけないのかな
"A certain commoner"
President, I simply can't
understand what this means.
部長 まるで意味がわかりません
ああ鏡夜 今ちょっと動いただろう こっち来て小指を繋げ
Are we sure that this man
isn't actually just a fool?
あの人 実はただのばかなのでは
視力落ちたんじゃないか
油断してはなりません
Do not let your guard down.
つべこべ言わずに 早く来い！
This is part of his strategy.
これは奴の作戦です
はいはい
Is that "some of the commoners"?
一部の庶民ですか
I hope this ends soon.
早く終わんないかな
Fujioka- kun, wasn't it?
藤岡君でしたね
Might I have a brief word with you?
少々お話を伺えますか
Okay.
Why did you join this club?
君はなぜこの部に
Oh, well, it was over me being
a little careless...
ちょっとした不注意で
You are an honor student, aren't you?
君は特待生ですよね
Yes, I am.
そうですけど
So in other words, you are a token
member of this club,
つまりその君が部の一員であることは
須王の家の権力誇示のための恰好の素材であるわけだ
here in order to allow the Suou family
to flaunt their power.
Huh?
彼の裏の顔について教えてもらえないか
Could I ask you to tell me
about his darker side?
Perhaps I will be able to help
you out of here, as well.
あるいは君を救う手助けにもなると思う
He doesn't have a darker side.
あの人に裏の顔なんて無いですよ
So, what? You're telling me that
those high school kids
じゃ何か
君は高校生の彼らが本気でこんな遊びを楽しんでいるとでも
genuinely enjoy playing these games?
Is that strange?
おかしいですか
It's not possible!
ありえないだろう
Chop!
切った
Hey! That's not where
you're supposed to cut, you know!
ほら そこは切るところじゃないぞ
Next, we're playing kick the can!
次 缶けり行くぞ
Kyoya, you're it, okay?
鏡夜が鬼だからな
Yeah.
All right...
Starlight kick!!
スターライトキック
If you think I'm going to fall
for the same trick again,
そう何度も同じ手が私に通用するとでも思って
you've got another thing com-
部長
President!
Haruhi, this way! Run!
ハルヒこっちだ 走れ
I don't think he has a darker side.
But come to think of it,
とても裏の顔のある人には思えない
でも そう言えば環先輩の家のことって何も知らないな
I don't know anything about
Tamaki-senpai's family, do I?
- One... two...
- You've got to be kidding me!
一 二 三 四 五 六
ったく冗談じゃない
- I can't put up with his
shenanigans any longer.
- Three... four...
これ以上彼の茶番には付き合いきれません
- You'll pay for this, Suou Tamaki.
- Five...
許すまじ 須王環
Six...
Are we lost?
迷ったんですか
迷ったんですね
We are lost, huh?
Hey, Haruhi,
ハルヒ ここにいい隠れ場所があるよ
there's a great hiding place over here!
We're lost.
迷ったんだ
In a sense, we're stranded, aren't we?
ある意味遭難ですね
Woof?
It's a good thing you made
Kyoya- senpai "it," isn't it?
鏡夜先輩を鬼にしといてよかったじゃないですか
Woof woof.
Are you goofing around?
ふざけてます？
Woof woof woof!
You know, I didn't think
I would be playing this game
でも高校生にもなって こんな遊びをするとは思いませんでした
once I got into high school.
This isn't fun?
楽しくないか
まあ 小学校の頃は友達とそれなりにやってましたけど
Well, I did play it with my friends
when we were in elementary school.
Uh-huh? You don't say.
そっか
I've never really had too many friends
俺は 同年代の友達があまりいなかったからな
who were the same age as me.
My mom got sick easily, you see?
うちの母が病気がちでね
I was so worried about her,
俺は心配で 表に出られない子供だったんだよ
I didn't go outside much as a child.
そして母を元気づけるために
And, to cheer my mom up,
I'd always sit and play
the piano beside her.
いつもそばでピアノを弾いたりしてた
That's why it's so fun for me
だから今はこうしてみんなと遊ぶのが楽しい
to play with everyone like this.
すごく楽しい
It's really fun!
Let's do this again.
またやろうな
Sure thing.
そうですね
I'm going to finish this story!
記事を仕上げます
But, President...
しかし部長
I think it might be too dangerous
証拠もないまま須王のゴシップなど書くのはあまりに危険かと
to write any gossip about
Suou without any proof.
Oh, even without any proof right now,
な～に 今は証拠がなくても奴が尻尾を出す記事を書けばいいのです
I just have to write
an article that exposes him.
If I set my mind to it,
I can cook up any number of articles
私が本気になれば
うちの学院のバカ連中が大騒ぎするぐらいの捏造記事は
that will throw the idiots
at this academy into a tizzy.
いくらでも書けるんです
"Newspaper Club"
In any case, we have to set Suou up.
とにかく須王の奴を陥れなければ
So, it is true.
やっぱりそうなんだ
きさまら
Why, you...
Although, it was pretty obvious.
ま バレバレだったけどね
I'll bet his highness is the only
one who hasn't caught on.
気づいてないの 殿くらいなんじゃない
He's especially dense
when it comes to himself.
あの人自分のことにはとりわけ疎いから
I'm warning you, if you start
something against his highness,
言っとくけど
うちの殿に手ぇ出したらただじゃ済まないよ
there will be consequences.
Are you ready to turn
not only the Hitachiins,
常陸院はもちろん うちの部全員の家を敵に回す覚悟あんの
but all of our club members'
families against you?
I knew it, Suou is wielding
his parents' power,
やはり親の権力を利用してその指示を出しているのが須王なんだな
and giving out orders to you!
No he isn't.
違うよ
Tama-chan wouldn't do that.
タマちゃんはそういうことしないよ
You know what?
あのね 僕らはタマちゃんのことが大好きだからね
We all love Tama-chan, and that's why.
He is a hopeless idiot, however.
どうしようもないバカだけどね
Kyoya...
鏡夜 俺と一緒に部を作ろう
Let's form a club together.
Hello, Haninozuka-senpai.
こんにちは 埴之塚先輩
I know this is sudden,
突然ですが 僕と一緒に部を立ち上げてみませんか
but would you like to form a club with me?
銛之塚先輩
Morinozuka-senpai!
You two don't seem to have anything to do.
君たち暇そうだな
If you're available,
暇ならどうだ 俺と一緒に部を立ち上げよう
what do you say to forming a club with me?
- So?
- What will it be?
どうするの
Don't do this, okay?
もうやめなよ こんなこと
ちくしょう
Damn it! It's not just Suou anymore,
もう須王だけじゃない お前ら全員破滅させてやる
I'm going to ruin all of you now!
"First-aid kit"
Please, feel free.
どうぞご自由に
However...
I wonder what you should
do about this disk,
させてもらったこのディスクは
which has been secretly recording
all of your remarks since yesterday.
どうすればいいのかな
部長
President!
No more!
これ以上は
To put it in the same terms
that you would, here's the deal.
あなた流のやり方で言うならこういうことです
You'd do well to remember
that with just the stock
うちの鳳グループと常陸院の持株だけでも
that the Otori Group
and the Hitachiins own,
あなたの父親の出版社なんて好きに社長を変えられることも
we could replace the president
of your father's publishing firm
whenever we like.
覚えておいたほうがいい
だけど 俺たちはあなたとは違うんです
However, we are not like you.
We are after fundamentally
different things.
目指しているものが根本的に違う
Found you!
見つけた
Woof!
Where's the Newspaper Club?
新聞部は
Something urgent came up,
so they've stopped covering us.
急用で取材中止だって
これからはまともな記事書くって言ってたよ
They said they'd be writing
respectable articles from now on.
Maybe they'll get by without
having to shut down their club.
廃部にならなくて済むんじゃない
Really? That's great, then.
そっか それならいいが
Let's hurry back to the club room
and eat some cake!
早く部室に帰ってケーキ食べよう
Yeah.
Yeah, sure. Cake! Cake!
そうですね
ケーキ ケーキ
Oh, by the way, Kyoya- senpai...
そういえば鏡夜先輩
Is the Suou family really
that big a deal?
須王の家って そんなにすごいんですか
Well, their industry has been based
まあ 事業としては古くから金融業を基盤に
around the finance business
for a long time.
You've heard of them, haven't you?
ほら 聞いたことないか
The Roy Grand Hotel,
the Outo Theatre, and so on?
ロワグランホテルとか桜都劇場とか
Also, as you know,
they are in school management.
あとはお前も知ってのとおり
学校経営と
What school?
どこの学校ですか
This one... Ouran.
この桜蘭だよ
You ought to at least know
who the superintendent
お前 自分の学校の理事長くらい 覚えといたほうがいいぞ
of your own school's board of trustees is.
That's right. Come to think of it now,
そうか よく考えてみれば
お前は環の家の援助で入学できたようなもんじゃないか
you were allowed to enroll here
with the aid of Tamaki's family,
weren't you?
See that you're grateful to them.
感謝しておけよ
Haruhi!
ハルヒ
Hurry up, or we're going
to leave you behind!
早くこないと置いてくよ
You'll get yourself lost again.
また迷子になっちゃいますよ
"The chairman's son"
From the moment I make my start,
the world expands.
なんとハルヒが行方不明になってしまった
What's this? Haruhi has gone missing!?
夏休みを利用して軽井沢にバイトに来てるだけです
I'm just using my summer vacation
to work in Karuizawa, that's all.
My refreshing self will come and see you!
爽やかなこの俺が会いに行ってやる
Next time, " The Refreshing
Battle in Karuizawa"
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ 来週も
Ouran High School Host Club will
be waiting for you, next week!
お待ちしております